刚收看我们节目不久的观众朋友 我们正在报道...
If you're joining us now, this is the update...
包揽全网头条的事件的最新进展
on the story which is still dominating the news today.
联邦调查局对韦斯达的突袭...
The FBI's dramatic raid on...
天哪
Oh, man!
这场突袭太有料了
There's so much good shit on the Waystar raid.
FBI于昨晚的突击检查中扣押了
韦斯达总部的来往邮件及文件
瞧啊
Look at that.
FBI于昨晚的突击检查中扣押了
韦斯达总部的来往邮件及文件
一目了然
Manifested.
FBI于昨晚的突击检查中扣押了
韦斯达总部的来往邮件及文件
继肯德尔·罗伊提出触目惊心指控后 FBI采取突击检查
很庆幸你跟他们不是一伙的 对吗 小格
You glad you're not on their team, huh, G?
继肯德尔·罗伊提出触目惊心指控后 FBI采取突击检查
是的
Oh, yeah.
当然
Totally.
怎么了
What's up?
没 没什么
Uh, no, nothing.
只是 你爸想见我...
Your dad just wants to see me, uh...
就在他的公寓见 立刻马上
uh, like, right away in his apartment, like, right now.
好吧
Okay.
去吧
Sure.
你该去见他
You should go.
-真的吗  -真的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
兄弟 这意味着你是有份量的 你是有用之人
It means you have weight, bro. You're an asset.
我只是... 我有个...
I just... I have like... this...
我有个挺傻的顾虑 如果我到了那儿
I have this, like, stupid worry that I'm gonna
发现那里有一群打手 走狗和大老粗
go over and there will be, like, goons and stooges
等着暴打我一顿怎么办
and rough-jacks there to administer a beating.
就是说 你怕他会挑拨你 让你背叛我
Well, honestly, he'll try to turn you against me.
对吧
Right?
-对  -没关系
- Yeah. - And that's fine.
因为你不会背叛我的
Because you're not gonna turn against me.
不 我不会背叛你的
No, no, no. No!
-不可能  -你会背叛我吗
- No way! - Are you gonna turn against me?
绝无可能 兄弟 我很坚定的
No way, man. I'm sturdy!
我是一只坚定的... 小鸟
I'm a sturdy... birdy.
这就对了
That's right!
兄弟 在公鸡打鸣之前默念三次
Say it three times before the cock crows, brother.
喔喔喔[公鸡打鸣的声音]
Cock-a-doodle-do!
大鸟 支棱起来
Okay, knuckle up, Big Bird.
-肯  -怎么了
- Ken? - Yeah?
所以 他们说这非常重要
So, they say it's super-high importance.
-约了五分钟  -约... 什么事
- Scheduled for five minutes. - Sc... What is?
我草
What the fuck?
你觉得他们... 他们以为自己能炒了我吗
You think they're... They think they can fire me?
-我觉得不行  -行吧
- No. - Yeah, okay. All right.
朋友们 我需要个指挥室
Hey, guys! I'm gonna need the command pod.
-你能清个场吗  -好的
- Can you clear the room? - Yeah.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 4 集
请在嘀声后说出您的名字
Please speak your name after the tone.
小霸王强干阿爹
Little Lord Fuckleroy.
请不要挂机 您拨打的会议正在连接中
Please hold while we connect you to your conference.
小霸王强干阿爹
Little Lord Fuckleroy.
...正在加入通话
... is now joining the call.
-哈喽  -肯德尔
- Hello, hello. - Hi, Kendall.
弗兰克 卡尔 西沃恩
You're on with, uh, Frank, Carl, Siobhan,
罗曼 卡洛丽娜 还有雨果也在线上
Roman, Karolina, Hugo,
-还有... -见鬼了
- and, um... - Wow! Holy shit!
大伙人都在呢 就像去他妈的...
Gang's all here, huh? It's like the fucking...
佩珀军士的破碎美企俱乐部[讽刺像披头士某专辑封面]
Sergeant Pepper of broken corporate America.
[佩珀军士的孤独之心俱乐部乐队(Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band)]
线上会议的段子可真是最棒的段子
Conference call jokes are just the best jokes, huh?
所以 我现在有点想挂断出去
So, now I'm thinking maybe I should terminate
拉上我的律师再回来聊
and dial back in with my own counsel.
-肯 只是随便聊聊  -你好哇 小西
- It's just a conversation, Ken. - Oh, hey, Shiv!
谢谢你的公开信
Thanks for the letter.
一流的创作
First-rate composition.
真他妈可怕啊
Really fucking horrible.
我可没胡编乱造
I didn't say anything that wasn't true.
你没有吗
Oh, no?
我希望这是值得的
Well, I hope it was worth it.
我不知道你我还能不能和好如初了
I don't know if me and you come back from that.
好的 知道了 老妈
Yeah, okay, well, sure, Mom.
不好意思
Excuse me.
小西 你确定你选对边了吗
You sure you picked the right side, Shiv?
-不好意思 我打断一下  -格丽 怎么了
- Excuse me! Excuse me! - Yeah, Gerri, what?
-肯德尔 我们现在遇到个麻烦  -确实 你们确实惹上麻烦了
- Kendall, we have a situation. - Yeah, you do have a situation.
-难道不是吗  -弗兰克 卡尔 你们能讲讲吗
- Don't you? - Uh, Frank, Karl, can you talk?
弗兰克现在要说了
Frank is going to speak now.
-肯 你好  -弗兰克
- Hey, Ken. - Hey, Frank.
司法部调查吹来的风 这个突袭
Yeah, the temperature of the DOJ investigation, the raid here,
对持股人产生了严重的反向效应
it's caused serious blowback from investors.
肯德尔 真是多谢你了
Yeah, thank you for that, Kendall.
问责就是扯淡
Hey, accountability's a fucker.
卡尔 特工找到你的乳头夹了吗
The Feds find your nipple clamps, Karl?
再说具体点
Specifically,
投资人指乔希·阿伦森和他百分之四的股份
Josh Aaronson and his four percent holding.
那个骗人的小婊砸
That chiseling little fuck.
他直接给格丽打了电话
He called Gerri direct and he's thinking
他在考虑跳到桑迪和斯图伊那边
of switching to Sandy and Stewy.
语气十分不满
And noisily.
肯 他已经一触即发了
His fingers on the big red button, Ken.
我们已经跟他谈了我们能提供什么
We've talked to him about what we can do
他在玩欲擒故纵 可是...
and he's playing hard to get. But...
他很想跟你和你爸一起坐下来聊聊
he was interested in time in the room with you and your dad.
我和我爸一起吗
Together?
不行
No.
我猜他是想了解事情的走向
Yeah, his thing was, I guess, to know how this goes.
他就是想讨回自己应得的东西[源自威尼斯商人]
He wants his pound of flesh, all right?
肯德尔 他只是想要确保
Uh, Kendall, he just wants to make sure
家族企业还能正常运转
that the family business can still function.
显然 我不能和我爸一起会面
Yeah, well, obviously, I can't meet jointly with Dad.
只不过是在律师办公室里聊半小时而已
It's just a half hour in a lawyer's office later.
肯德尔 距离股东大会只有四天了
Kendall, we are four days out from the shareholder meeting.
肯德尔 这事关公司的掌控权
Kendall, it's about control of the company, all right?
票数情况岌岌可危
The vote is on a razor's edge.
我们需要他这百分之四
We need his four percent.
除非你觉得我们中的任何一个人会有更光明的未来
Unless you think that any of us would have a bright future
在桑迪和斯图伊掌控了公司后
with Sandy and Stewy in control of the firm.
所以 他提议四个小时后...
So, um, he's suggesting in four hours...
行了 行了 你没资格催我做决定
No, no, no. No! You don't railroad me. No.
我需要跟我的团队商量
I need to run this by my team.
我和我爸一起 看上去就很不和谐
Me and Dad together, the optics are janky as fuck.
来吧 来好好表现
Come! Behave appropriately!
你好哇 老爸
Oh, hey, Dad!
拜托 我什么时候表现不好了
Come on, when have I ever not behaved appropriately?
这样对我是行不通的
This just doesn't work for me.
再见了您嘞 愿上帝保佑你
So, fuck you and God bless.
小霸王强干阿爹
Little Lord Fuckleroy.
...下线了
... has left the call.
如果他不去 会有多糟呢
If he doesn't go, how bad is it?
我听说突袭只是个警告
Well, I'm hearing that the raid was just a warning shot.
所以现在情况应该会平静下来
So, things should settle down now.
我觉得我需要找更多人
I think I need more people.
更多层保险
More protection.
爸 你有两个前司法部副部长
Dad, you have two former Deputy AG's
还有前司法部欺诈调查主管
and the ex-head of Fraud at Main Justice.
这些人就是你的哈林篮球队[世界上最受欢迎的篮球队]
These are the Harlem Globetrotters,
他们能搞翻威斯特彻斯特的法官们
the Westchester Judge-fuckers.
那老家伙欠了我一个世界
The Raisin owes me everything.
而现在我需要一些掩护
And now I need a bit of fucking cover,
这个白眼狼就玩儿消失了
the forgetful cunt's gone AWOL.
从新闻角度来说
I think perhaps, we have been insufficiently rigorous,
我觉得我们对总统还不够严酷
journalistically, on the President.
你觉得给他点压力 他会更好地回应吗
You think he'll respond well to a little bit of pressure?
每次我打给米歇尔·安
Well, every time I call Michelle-Anne,
她都跟我说 "耐心点
she tells me, "Be Patient!
援兵正在来的路上"
The cavalry is coming!"
我需要筹码
I need leverage.
康纳又打过来了
I have Connor, again.
看见了吗 我被逼到死胡同了
See? See? I'm in a corner.
每个人都想分一杯羹
Everyone wants a piece.
每个人都在打破常规 所有事情都一起来了
Everyone's out of their box. Everything's coming up fuck.
我希望你多盯着点 好吗
I want you on fire-watch, okay?
好的 老爸 我会的
Yeah, okay, Dad. Absolutely.
还有 盯着谈判
And, uh, watch the negotiations.
卡尔是个聪明的混蛋
Karl's a smart bastard
但是 他想要别人喜欢他
but, uh, he likes to be liked.
-不太有利  -懂了
- Not good. - Got it.
所以我们能制定一下战略吗 我有些金点子
Okay, so can we strategize? I got potential gold here.
但我需要你看看怎么部署
But I need your read on how to deploy.
罗曼 你能把袜子和鞋穿上吗
Roman, could you please put your footwear on?
为了能更好地合作 我们需要界限感
Uh, see, for this to work, we need, you know, boundaries.
-还有... -什么 我还不能脱鞋了
- And... - What, I can't take my footwear off?
只是...
Well, it's just...
怎么 我不能自己选择自慰的时间和地点了吗
What, I can't masturbate in a time and place of my choosing?
-你看  -你在建造...
- See that? - You are building...
-这样会毁了我们  -...一个警察国家 格丽
- That will kill us. - ... A police state here, Gerri.
[通过警察部门控制人民旅行及言论自由]
我找到那个纹身男了
I found tattoo man.
-"纹身男"吗  -对
- "Tattoo man"? - Yup.
那是个有趣的小故事 大概在十五年前
Funny little story. So, about fifteen-ish years ago,
肯德尔在新奥尔良开单身派对 我们好像是...
Kendall's bachelor party in New Orleans, we did this, like...
在波旁街不停地转场各个酒吧
ironic bar crawl thing on Bourbon Street.
我们还和那些
And we got chatting with this, you know,
友好的流浪汉聊天
friendly hobo.
聊了聊作为流浪汉 不得不做的一些...
And there was talk of, you know, various...
恶心的挣扎 比如
disgusting endeavors like, you know,
"流浪汉会吃油炸帆船鞋吗"
"Would the hobo eat a deep-fried deck shoe?"
很蠢的 反正都是屁话
You know, stupid, whatever, bullshit.
但我们提了一个...
Before we settled on a rather...
非常不光彩的想法 那就是...
indecent proposal which was to...
让那个无家可归的人
get the homeless man to have
把肯德尔的名字纹在他的额头上
Kendall's name tattooed on his forehead.
什么
What?
对 我们把肯德尔名字的缩写纹在了一个陌生人脸上
Yeah, we got Kendall's initials tattooed on a rando.
而你觉得翻出这事是个好主意吗
And you think this is a good idea to dredge this up?
来黑肯德尔—恍然大悟公主吗
On Kendall? Woke-ahontas?
用一个可怜的额头当做便利贴的故事吗
Using a poor's forehead as a Post-It?
这他妈是个杀手锏 你在开玩笑吗
It's fucking killer, are you kidding me?
好吧 我不太确定
Well, I'm not so sure.
好吧 那我们可以午饭的时候聊聊吧
Okay, well, we can talk about it over lunch, maybe?
今天不行 罗曼 我有约了
Uh, not today, Roman, I have a date.
去他妈的 和谁 蒙哥马利·克利夫特么[好莱坞黑白电影演员]
Fuck off! With who? Montgomery Clift?
-昔日圣诞幽灵吗  -是劳里
- The Ghost of Christmas Past? - Laurie.
-谁  -劳里
- Who? - Laurie.
他之前在司法部
He's ex-DOJ.
参与了安达信诉讼
He worked the Arthur Anderson prosecution.
我想知道会不会有后门可以走
I want to see if there's a back channel there.
劳里
Laurie?
你说他想要在停车场开你的后门吗...
And you said he wants to back-channel you in the parking lot or...
是的 关键是我有交往对象了
Yeah, so, the thing is, I'm dating.
而且我需要被理解
I am dating and that needs to be understood.
好的 我知道了
Okay, I get it. Yeah, yeah.
你在划界限
You're drawing a line.
否则的话...
Or otherwise, you know...
劳里非要把我这老身骨虐散架不可
Laurie will knock my jolly old block off.
如果他能...
If he can...
找到他藏剑的手杖
find his sword stick
然后发动他的机动浴椅的话[用来推病人或老人]
and fire up his motorized bath chair.
好嘞
All right.
早上好
Good morning!
格雷格
Greg.
喝点吧
Drink.
喝酒吗
Uh, alcohol?
当然 我... 现在挺早的 但我...
sure, I... It's early but I...
好 我想要一杯朗姆酒兑可乐
Yeah, I think I'll actually have me a nice glass of rum and coke.
凯莉
Kerry!
可以帮格雷格拿点可口可乐吗
Can we bring, uh, Greg some Coca-Cola?
不 没关系的
No, it's fine really.
-她不需要...  -不 不 不
- Uh, she doesn't have to... - No, no, no.
格雷格想要的... 必须得到
What Greg wants... Greg must have.
谢谢你 真是好得太离... 我不知道
Thank you. Like, so kind. Ridicu... I don't know.
你和肯德尔最近经常在一起
You and Kendall have been hanging around a lot.
对吗
Correct?
我在...
I am, um...
只是普通社交关系
It's purely social, you know.
问题是如果你和他纠缠太多...
The thing is your position at Waystar...
你在韦斯达的位置可能会变得复杂
could become complicated if you get too associated with him.
你明白吗
You can see that?
好浓啊
Strong.
好喝但很浓 很浓
Nice and strong. Strong one.
浓得像男人喝的
Strong for a man.
联邦调查局近来一直在搜查我们的办公室
The FBI, as you know, have been poking around our offices.
格雷格...
Greg...
你以前应该没遇到过这种事
you've probably never done this before.
我们都非常 非常地担心
And we're all, all very, very concerned.
我不想看到你受牵连
I don't want to see you hurt.
我们需要咱们的律师团结合作
We need our lawyers all working together.
作为一个和谐的大家庭
One big happy family.
联合辩护协议 庞大又坚固的保护伞
Joint Defense Agreement. Big strong umbrella.
让你免于淋雨
Keeps you dry.
那... 有意思 很有意思
That... it's interesting. It's very interesting.
我想我得和我的律师皮尤谈一谈
I think I would have to speak to my lawyer, uh, Pugh,
通常在白天联系不到他
who is often unavailable during daytime.
我们为你准备好了需要签署的文件
We have the paperwork ready for you to sign.
好吧
Right.
所以那 我猜
So, okay, I guess...
我的问题是...
my question would be...
这值什么呢
what's it worth?
"我"在这之中值什么呢
In terms of the "Me" Of it all?
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想要什么吗 我的意思是...
What do I want? I mean...
我能得到什么呢
What can I get?
不是这样玩的
That's not the way it works.
可能就是
Well, maybe it is.
看看你自己 抖得像他妈一片树叶
Look at you. Shaking like a fucking leaf.
听着
Listen.
你有一些筹码 就一点点
You have some leverage. Just a little.
所以 你还是先滚蛋
So, why don't you fuck off
回去想一想到底什么才能让你站在我们这边
and think about what you wanna ask for to come on side
我再看看我能做些什么
and I'll see what I can do.
好吗
Okay?
公平
Fair.
公平的交易 不是交易 是个计划
Fair deal. Not a deal. But a plan.
我要一口... 一口闷吗还是
Shall I chug... chug this or?
我能... 我能一口干掉它
I can... I can chug it.
好的 谢谢你 洛根
Good. Thank you, Logan.
好吧
Oh, good.
我不知道你们在六十年代是怎么做到的
I don't know how you did it back in the 60s.
时代不同了 真的时代不同了
Different times. Different times indeed.
更好的时代吗
Better times?
不... 不见得
Not... Not for all.
怎么了 老古董
Yo, what's up, Ancient Grains?
只是想知道你在想什么
Just wanna see where your head's at.
你没资格催我做决定
Yeah, you don't railroad me.
不行的 弗兰克
Not going, Frank.
-杰西  -什么
- Jess. - Yes?
-接一下视频 拍兔子给孩子们  -没问题
- Rabbit-cam, for the kids. - Great.
肯 假如事情真按你的计划发展
Ken, say this all blows up the way you intend,
你爸退位了 你一定希望
your dad's gone. You're going to need
大怪兽睡在你身后的那个巢穴吧
the big beasts in your corner afterwards.
所以呢
Uh-huh?
我已经完全控制了乔希·阿伦森
Well, Josh Arenson is a lock for me.
他一直都是坚实的后盾
He's always been a lock right back.
他可不是这么跟别人说的
That's not what he says to people.
听着 这样做是明智的 你明白的
Look, it's smart to do this. You know it is.
目前这样是明智的 因为你不能让桑迪和斯图伊赢
It's smart for now because you can't have Sandy and Stewy win.
对吧 那会像核弹般毁了一切
Right? That just nukes everything.
我知道 但他们会和解...
Yeah, but they'll settle...
最终会和解 对吧
in the end, right?
但为了明天那也是明智的
But also it's smart for tomorrow because it would be fun if,
因为如果你爸必须退出
if... your dad has to step away,
你有机会向阿伦森展示你自己
you get to show Aaronson who you are.
何时何地
When and where?
我说了不算
Change of venue.
都是最后时刻决定 乔希的女儿病了
It's all last minute. Josh's daughter is sick,
所以他要求你去他的岛
so he requests that you go out to his island.
好吧
Uh-huh?
这是个意外收获对吧 低调点
It's a bonus, right? Discreet.
还有一个建议就是
There's a suggestion you convene
你和你父亲在另一头的停机坪上碰头十分钟
with your father for ten minutes on the tarmac at the other end.
只是为了
Just to, you know,
达成共识 排除尴尬
agree on approach, flush out any awkwardness.
我会告知你的
I'll let you know.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那个 他们要求我们在这稍等一下
Um, okay, we're actually being asked to hold for just one second.
好吧
Okay.
先生 这边请
Sir, you're this way.
不 那给叛徒坐
No, for the Judas.
我坐这架直升机
I'll take this one.
好了 换我们移动了
Um, okay, you're... We're good.
你要确保兔子有水喝
Just make sure the rabbit has water.
好
Yeah.
他们叫我们先出发
They've asked us to take off first.
他不想先到那等你
He doesn't want to wait at the other end.
-你好啊  -你好
- Hey! - Hey.
爸想要我台一个主播 出面批评政府
So, Dad would like a host out criticizing the administration.
你想告诉雷文海德还是希德
You wanna tell Ravenhead or Cyd?
不是这样办事的 西沃恩
Well, that's not really how it works, Siobhan.
我们必须小心翼翼地对待我台的支柱
We'd have to handle a pivot like that very delicately.
这我知道 汤姆
Well, I know that, Tom.
但我以为跟我丈夫说话
But I thought I was talking to my husband,
不用转弯抹角呢
so I could be a little more direct.
好 但正如我说的 这是件无比复杂的事情 所以
Okay, well, as I say, it's a very complex situation, so
那是什么...
What's, uh...
这个吗 只是在评估一些设施
What's this? Just, um... just ranking the facilities.
汤姆 那不会...
Tom, that's not...
那不会发生的
That's not gonna happen.
不不不 我知道 只是...
No, no, no, I know. But, uh...
假设会发生 我更倾向于首选奥蒂斯维尔监狱
if it does, I'm leaning towards FCI Otisville as my number one.
奥蒂斯维尔吗 那是...
Otisville? That's the...
-在马里兰的监狱吗  -不是
- the prison in Maryland? - No.
才不是
No.
坎伯兰才是在马里兰的监狱
Cumberland is the prison camp in Maryland.
小西 奥蒂斯维尔是在纽约州北部 那个犹太人监狱好吗
Shiv, Otisville is upstate. You know, the Jewish jail?
对 对的
Yes, right.
对的 抱歉
Right, sorry.
我只是对那里的优点一直有所耳闻
I just keep hearing a lot of really good things about it.
自动贩卖机和结实的床铺等
Kosher vending machines and sturdy bunks and...
汤姆 这只是个假设
Tom. It's an "If".
一个很大 很操蛋的假设
A really big fucking "If".
你知道人们叫我绝症汤姆吗
You know they're calling me Terminal Tom,
楼下七楼的人吗
down on seven?
因为我身患的是业界癌症
'Cause I've got cancer of the career.
总之 谁该去告诉马克我们得鸣枪示警
So, who tells Mark we need to send a shot across the bow?
雷文海德有他自己的军队 他...
You know, Ravenhead has his own battalions. He, uh...
他重视独立的话语权
He values his independence.
他就是小婊子
He's a little bitch.
一旦他怂了 就会对我爸百依百顺了
Once he gets it, he'll do what my dad wants.
怎么 白人至上主义的电台会付他三千万的年薪吗
What? White Pride FM gonna pay him 30 mil a year?
但他会很介意
Well, he's not gonna like it.
你会处理这事的对吧
But you'll handle it?
我... 我会去处理 但是...
I mean... Yeah, I'll do it. But...
但从观感上来说
But in terms of, you know, optics,
我可能不应该听命于你
I should probably not take orders from you.
过多地
Much.
因为... 因为企业管理
Because of... Because of corporate governance.
企业管理吗
Corporate governance?
对 你懂的...
Yeah, like, you know...
从集团架构表来说
Like in terms of the org chart.
还有 我的男子气概...
And my... masculinity. I... You know.
如果你不听我的 这会削弱我的权威
If you carve out from me, it undermines me.
反过来会削弱我啊 如果我看向墙上的集团架构表
But it undermines me if I look at the wall and the org chart
上面写着我正被我老婆从后面操
suggests that you're being fucked in the ass by your wife!
汤姆 我要你去搞定雷文海德 好吗
Tom. I would like you to handle Ravenhead, yeah?
好的 我会跟他聊聊
Sure, I'll talk to him.
还有 你能去搞定格雷格吗[用拇指夹刑]
And can you thumb-screw Greg?
我们需要他签署联合辩护协议
We need him under the Joint Defense.
好的
Sure.
我待会来检查 好吗
I'll check in later, yeah?
他人在哪 他的车呢
Where is he? Where's his car?
我马上联系他
I'm trying him now.
-喂  -肯德尔 洛根在等你
- Yeah. - Uh, Kendall, I have Logan for you.
我们在停机坪这 等着和你对齐话术
We're holding on the tarmac for the catch-up.
对 但听着 我觉得我们该说什么 各自挺清楚的
Yeah, hey, so look, I think it's pretty obvious what we need to say,
所以我直接去乔希的家了
so I'm headed straight to Josh's compound.
告诉老爸 "哔哔"
Tell Dad, "Meep-Meep!"
这是"流浪者"里的梗
It's from Road Runner.
你好啊 人来啦
Hey! There he is!
-你好啊  -你好
- Hey! - Hi.
瞧瞧你 老妹
Look at you, sis.
你需要我们的什么协助吗
So, what can we do for you here?
我想当个不惹事的小男孩
Well, I wanna be a good little boy,
而且对你们有用处的
and I wanna be useful.
但我觉得我需要点甜头
But I think I need me some pie here.
好 我先开始说 还是你
Okay, so shall I go? Or will you?
我们很期待能和你更紧密地合作
You know, we're very excited about the idea of working more closely with you.
好极了 在政场上
Great. Okay, politically,
我时常因为缺乏工作经验而被针对
a lack of real-world experience has sometimes been leveled at me.
尤其现在 谣言说
Ah, now, even with the rumors,
老家伙极有可能连任
the Raisin is likely gonna win again.
因此 我打算四年后再尝试
So, I'm looking to make my move in four.
总之 这期间我想要
Therefore, I wouldn't be uninterested
进入公司
in coming in
并达成...三到四个成就后 再离开公司
and hitting... three-four major achievements and then getting out.
行吧 康纳 我跟你摊牌
Okay, all right, Connor. Cards on the table.
我们在考虑给你美食家频道
We were thinking of offering you Gourmando.
美食家吗
Gourmando?
我觉得美食类频道不太适合我
I really don't see myself at a food network.
你可以做个 品酒节目
You could do, uh, a wine tasting show.
你真心觉得我在镜头前吐出里奥哈红酒
You really think that me spitting out rioja on camera
会帮助我赢得中西部的民心吗
is going to help me win the rust belt?
但是康纳 我真不觉得我们能让你
But, Connor, I just don't think we can give you
在当下局势之中 担任一个高级管理职位
a high-level executive role in the current climate.
听着 老妹
Look, sis.
我不喜欢胁迫老人家 但我要这么做
I don't like having my boot on the old man's throat, but I do.
我还是多少有点能耐
I got me some juice.
- 有点吧  -不不不
- Well, up to a point. - Oh, no, no, no, no.
我随时都可以拿出大喇叭 然后喊
I can pull out the old megaphone anytime I want and I can say,
"知道吗
"Hey! Guess what?
我记得我父亲是个肮脏
I recall my father was a nasty,
种族歧视 不尽职的人
racist, neglectful individual.
曾经人们在这都说什么来着
What was it that they used to say around here?
四楼以上 黑人犹太人以及女人免进
No Blacks, no Jews, no women above the fourth floor".
你已经得到了我们的注意 康纳
You already have our attention, Connor.
-很好  -我只是以为
- Good. - I just thought
一个生活类频道 或是家畜饲养
a lifestyle network or, you know, a stock situation
会比较对口你的专业
would be easier for you to manage.
你还记得... 你曾经
Remember... remember when you had that, uh,
角色扮演过邮局吗
play post office?
你曾将所有寄到家里的信件盖章
And you used to stamp all the mail that came into the house?
对
Yeah.
有点像现在对吧 小西
This is a little bit like that. Isn't it, Shiv?
咱们理性讨论 康纳
Let's stay civil, Connor.
我不想和你讨价还价 小西
I just don't think I wanna deal with you, Shiv.
你好啊 你在呢
Hey, hey! There he is!
-乔希 你好吗  -你好啊
- Josh, what's up! - Hey!
肯德尔 你好吗
Kendall! How are you?
见到你很高兴 老兄
Good to see you, man.
-你还好吗  -好 很好
- You okay? - Yeah, good.
很好 很好
Good, good.
谢谢你来
Thanks for coming out.
开玩笑吗 只要你一句话
Are you kidding? You just had to say the word.
凯蒂还好吗
How's Kitty?
她还好 好多了 说起来有点蠢
She's, uh, good. Better. It was dumb.
今早她发烧了
She had a fever this morning.
-但是  -真操蛋
- But, um... - Fuck.
...我不想费劲进城
... I just didn't wanna come into the city.
希望你不介意
I hope that's okay?
你家的艾弗森 还好吗
How's your, uh... Iverson?
-挺好 挺好的  -是吗
- Yeah, great. Great. - Yeah?
我刚给他买了个神他妈大的兔子
I just bought him a fucking giant rabbit.
现在他在谷歌搜索
So, now he's, like, Googling
哪里能买到世上最大的胡萝卜
where he can buy the world's biggest carrot.
-这太他妈好笑了  -绝了
- That's fucking hilarious. - It's good.
太好笑了
Hilarious.
-出来看看吧  -好啊
- Come outside. Take a look. - Yeah.
-这地方不错  -是啊
- Nice spot. - Yeah.
那么 老头子呢
So, where's the big man?
没什么事 他... 他有个电话要接
Ah, it's all good. He... he had to take a call.
让我先来了
He sent me ahead.
确定没什么事吗
It's all good?
我不知道 确实 有好有坏吧
I don't know. Sure. It's all terrible. It's all good.
你知道的 无所谓了
You know. Whatever.
对吧
Right?
我不知道 我想问的就那么多
I don't know. I guess that's my whole question.
我们还是等老头子来吧
We should probably wait for the old man.
但是 你看 情况挺糟糕的
But yeah, look, it's a fuck-pie.
但到头来 也没有那么复杂
But end of the day, it's not that complicated.
比如 我比我爸强
Like, I'm better than my dad.
但我爸还是比桑迪和斯图伊强
But my dad is still better than Sandy and Stewy.
好吧 我的另一个选择是 我... 退出
Yeah. My other option is, I... just get out.
这样的话...
Well...
巨变要来了
the comet is coming.
我想启动一次收购
I think a single acquisition.
买进一个现成的用户界面
We buy in an oven-ready UI.
机器学习 社交媒体 超级应用之类的玩意儿
Machine learning, social media, super app dinges.
-我们买下GoJo  -这个...
- We buy GoJo. - Uh-huh.
有点贵了
It's a little overpriced.
我不知道
I don't know.
优秀的用户界面和糟糕的内容
Great UI, shitty content,
遇到了糟糕的用户界面和优秀的内容
meet shitty UI, great content.
你知道的 我喜欢你 抛开这一切 我真的...
You know, I like you. Outside of all this, I really...
我真的很喜欢你
I really like you.
我也喜欢你 伙计
I like you too, pal.
我的四十岁生日派对会很疯狂
Big fucking nervous breakdown of a party for my fortieth.
-你一定要来  -好 还有谁去
- You gotta come. - Yeah, who's going?
什么 你要看一下宾客名单吗
What, you need the list?
你 我 还有亨利·基辛格
You, me, and Henry Kissinger!
去你的 我人脉广得很
Fuck you! I know everybody.
一定棒极了
It's gonna be the bomb.
很棒 是的
Oh, cool, yeah, yeah.
-我们应该多在一起玩  -是啊
- We should hang more. - Yeah. Yeah.
你好啊
Hey!
船长 我的船长
Captain, my Captain!
乔希
Josh!
你女儿怎么样了
How's your daughter?
我想她会没事的
I think she will be fine.
谢谢你远道而来
Hey, thanks for, uh, coming all this way.
客气了 我了解那种感觉
Oh, not at all. I know what it's like.
是啊 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
那么...
So...
-你好 儿子  -你好 爸
- Hello, son. - Hey, Dad.
请坐吧
Grab a seat.
那么...
So, uh...
劳驾你们跑这么远
Sorry for all this.
我知道你们都很忙
Look, I know you're pressed for time.
我只是想问一下
I just wanted to, uh, check in.
作为一个持股人 同时也是作为...
As an investor, but, uh, you know, also as a...
一个朋友
as a friend.
我有点担心
You know, I guess I have concerns.
我摸着良心告诉你
Let me tell you, hand on heart.
无论短期内局势如何动荡
Whatever the turbulence in the short term,
都不会出现任何大问题
there is nothing that's a significant issue.
核心业务就是核心业务
The core business is the core business
波动已经反映在现在的股价中了
and the volatility is priced in now.
今后将都是利好
So, it's all upside from here.
最安全的选择就是支持我 坚持立场
Safest option, back me, sit tight,
在你的城堡里数你的金子
counting your gold in your castle here,
我会让你盆满钵满
and I'll make you whole.
行吗
Okay?
不 那样不行 我们能出去走走吗
No, it doesn't work like that. Can we take a walk?
看看这个纽约自大狂
Look at this fucking New York wiseacre.
不 说真的 来吧
No, seriously, come on.
这里美得不像话...
It's so beautiful, it's disgusting. I mean...
散个步吗
A walk?
-是的  -多远
- Yeah. - How far?
来吧 爸 出去走走
Come on, Dad. Let's walk it out.
行吗
Yeah?
需要帮你叫辆代步车吗 还是我们步行去
Shall I send the cart for you, or shall we walk?
当然 步行吧
Sure! Let's walk.
好 很好 我喜欢
Good, good. Nice! Love it!
金刚与我共舞
Fucking King Kong come out to dance with me.
我很荣幸
I'm honored.
我马上就回来
Uh, I'll be right back.
好了 他们来了
Okay, here they come.
该死的纹身男
Fucking tattoo man!
-谢谢你们能来  -你好啊 伙计
- And thank you for coming. - Hey! Hey, man.
-你好  -你...
- Hi. - How, uh...
你好吗 气色不错啊
How you doing? You look great.
-谢谢  -你好
- Thank you. - Hi.
很高兴再次见到你
Good to see you again.
什么 是的 不 很高兴...
What? Oh, yeah, no. Good to...
我也很高兴见到你 能叙叙旧真好
Good to see you too. It's good to catch up, um...
你一直没有联系我
You never call!
-雨果 你有话要说吗  -是的
- Hugo, do you wanna? - Yes.
所以我们想跟阿尔伯斯库先生
So, we wanted to make an offer
谈一笔交易
to Mr. Albescu.
这属于保密协议的范围吗
Is this an NDA situation?
抱歉 但是 我不是想哔哔哔
Sorry, but, uh, I'm not trying to be a dick here.
但是 我看到...
But, uh, I'm looking. And, um...
我想说 你是...
Yeah, I'm just gonna say. You're the...
你就是那个人 对吧
You're the guy, right?
纹身是在那里吗
Is it there?
经过四年 他把...
After a four-year period, he had the...
那个标志 那个设计 去掉了...
insignia, the design removed...
-好吧  -...以此来提高就业潜力和社会接受度
- Huh. - ... in order to improve employment potential and social acceptability.
好吧...
Well...
可惜了
that's a shame.
我是说 我觉得你的那个标志很有特色
I mean, I think you really had something there.
对你来说很有效
It was really working for you.
抱歉 我能不能
Uh, sorry, can I just?
不介意吧
Do you mind?
好
Okay.
-雨果 你能来看看吗  -好的
- Hugo? Could you? - Yeah, uh...
-那么...  -借过
- So... - Excuse me.
...隐约可以看到 对吧
... you can sort of see it, right?
看 很明显是三个字母
See, it's clearly three digits.
我能辨认出这里的R 但看不太清...
I can make out the "R" Here. But I don't really see...
你觉得这像个K吗
Like, does that look like a "K" To you?
不 不 我们应该... 不
No, no. We should... No.
好了...
Okay, um...
所以 你有那时候的照片吗
So, do you have any, um, photos of it from around then?
如果你有照片 我们会支付一笔赔偿金
We'd arrange payment if you had any photos.
好吧 我并不为自己当时的行为感到骄傲
Yeah, I'm not super proud of what I did.
所以我不想看到任何照片流出去
So, wouldn't want any photos of it out there.
对 很有道理 不想...
Right, that makes sense. And not wishing to...
把这件事当作一笔交易 但是...
uh, make this too transactional, but...
这些照片要多少钱
how much for the photos?
我真的...
I really...
这感觉不太好
It doesn't feel good.
感觉像是回到了过去
It would feel like going backwards.
是的 有道理
Yeah, that makes sense.
但总能开个价吧 对吧
But there's gotta be a number. Right?
我...
I...
那就一百万吧
I'm just gonna say a million dollars.
一百万
Million dollars?
她好多了吧
She's feeling better, huh?
是啊 是不是很神奇
Yeah, isn't that amazing?
一小时前她还躺在床上
She was in bed an hour ago.
乔希 告诉我你想要什么吧
So, Josh, why don't you tell me what you want.
我看看能不能满足你 然后就可以滚蛋了
I'll see if I can give it to you and we can fuck off.
低血糖
Low blood sugar.
要我回去
You want me to run back
帮你拿根香蕉或者能量棒什么的吗
and grab you a banana, or a power bar, or something?
因为我真的很想聊一下这个话题
'Cause I'd really like to get into this.
好吧 走吧
Okay, let's go.
好
Okay.
我亏损了百分之四股权中的百分之十
I've lost ten percent of my four percent on this.
三亿五千万美元
Three-hundred and fifty million dollars.
理想情况下 我想拿回来
Ideally, I'd like to get it back.
所以 我想归根结底还是在于
So, uh, I guess it comes down to
你跟桑迪谁能帮我把钱赚回来
are you or Sandy gonna get me that back?
跟我们干
Stick with us.
坚守我们的价值主张
Stick with the value proposition.
我们代表行业的未来
This is the industry vision,
-未来在这里诞生  -对
- right here. - That's right.
可是你们怎么做得到呢
But how does that work?
你已经说了那些话
After what you've said,
这公司怎么还开得下去
how the hell does that work?
知道吗 披头士成员起诉对方的那段时间里
Well, you know, Beatles put out some of their best shit
出了他们最牛的作品
when they were suing each other.
不是吗
Right?
是啊 他们很牛
Yeah, good band.
伟大的乐队
Great band.
是很牛
Good band.
好吧
Right.
咚咚咚
Knock-knock!
是汤姆啊
Oh, hey, Tom!
绝症汤姆来访啦
Terminal Tom calling!
庆功宴上的幽灵
The ghost at the feast.
洗白用的海绵
The shame sponge.
别这样
No, no.
我刚刚被雷文海德狠狠喷了一顿
I just got my clock cleaned by Ravenhead.
-不会吧  -是真的
- No? - Yeah.
不过没关系 工作而已
But it's cool. It's just the job.
我说这个只当是说个笑话
I only mention it to amuse.
好吧 很有趣
Cool. That's funny.
现在我被派到这里来上拇指夹
Yeah, now I've been sent down here to apply the thumb screws.
真惨
Oh, no.
是欢迎新成员的小点心
Oh, courtesy pastries, huh?
是啊 我感觉大家对我太好了点
Yeah, I think I'm... I think I'm being courted a bit.
所以...
So...
我在考虑要作何选择
Well, I guess I'm... I'm considering my options.
很好
Good.
很好 格雷格 说实话
Good. You know, Greg, honestly,
你基本上可以提任何要求
you can probably ask for whatever you want.
是吗
Yeah?
好吧...
Well, um...
虽然我很感激泛美网科 还有你
All due respect to ATN. And you.
但是我... 我觉得我想管游乐园
But I... I feel that where my heart is, is parks.
-那好啊  -真的
- Okay. - Really.
我觉得我更喜欢做体验经济
I think ex... experience economy is maybe where it's at.
那就来展望一下吧
Let's game this out!
-来啊 想想看你要怎么做  -好吧
- Come on, let's game it out. - Okay.
-我在想要一个运营主管的位置  -不错
- So, I was thinking of asking for Operations Director. - Yeah.
-然后踢掉雷  -不错 雷是个混球
- Then kill Ray. - Yes, Ray's an asshole.
然后 你大概就可以亲自主持大局了
And then, maybe, I think, you know, start hands on.
就是这样 从一个二级游乐园入手
No, exactly, yeah. Get it in at a tier two park.
再要一个"明亮星水牛"的代理权
Ask for deputy at, like, Brightstar Buffalo,
这样我周末还可以回家
so I'm home on weekends.
-小菜一碟  -没错
- Easy-peasy. - Right!
太好了
Perfect!
你应该早就计划过了吧
So, I guess you've already gamed it.
对
Yeah.
不过还是谢... 谢谢你
But, thank... thank you.
我刚突然想到一个非常好笑的点 格雷格
An amusing notion has just occurred to me, Greg.
-什么  -对啊
- Yeah? - Yes.
你要去管主题公园了
You're gonna be running a theme park.
而我 要蹲监狱去了
And here's me, going to jail.
你马上就要住进魔法城堡
And you're gonna be living in a magical castle.
而我会被打入地牢
And I am going to be down in a dungeon
在里面跪舔巨魔 只求他们给我个电话卡
somewhere, sucking off ogres for phone cards.
不会的 谁也不知道事情会变成什么样
No, I mean, who even knows?
我说的这些可能没用呢...
This probably won't work...
格雷格 你知不知道...
Greg what do you know about, um...
尼禄[罗马皇帝]和斯普鲁斯
Nero and Sporus?
尼禄和...
Nero and...
斯普鲁斯
Sporus.
-斯普鲁...  -对
- Spor... - Greg, yeah.
斯普鲁斯是个年轻的男仆
Sporus was a young slave boy.
他是尼禄的最爱 后来...
He was Nero's favorite. And, uh...
你知道尼禄对他做了什么吗
you know what Nero did to him?
"尼禄和斯普鲁斯" 我不知道...
"Nero and Sporus". I don't...
我不熟悉这个IP
This is not IP I'm familiar with.
尼禄...
Well, Nero...
把他自己的老婆...
pushed his wife...
推下了楼梯
down the stairs.
然后他把斯普鲁斯阉了
And then he had Sporus castrated
娶了他代替他老婆
and he married him instead.
尼禄给了他一枚戒指
And he gave him a ring.
命令斯普鲁斯打扮成亡妻的样子
And he made him dress up like his dead wife.
哇
Wow!
大反转啊 没想到还有这手
Plot twist! Didn't see that coming.
是啊 我买了一本讲罗马人的书 准备带到监狱里读
Yeah, I bought a book on the Romans to read in prison.
-那本书特别厚  -是本好书吗
- It's a big book. - Well, is it a good book?
当然 写得相当好
It's a decent book, yeah.
我也会阉了你 然后马上娶你
I'd castrate you and marry you in a heartbeat.
-你没事吧 汤姆  -那啥
- Are you okay, Tom? - Hey!
格雷格 我们来试试你能不能把我摔到地上
See if you can wrestle me into the ground, Greg.
-不要吧  -来啊
- No. - Come on.
-我不想...  -来啊来啊...
- I don't want to... - Come on. Let's...
让我们像鸡一样打一架
Come on, let's fight like chickens.
-不了 我...  -快来
- No, I... - Come on!
快啊 我们来一场小型拳击比赛
Come on! Come on. Let's have a little punching match.
不了吧
No, no.
快点 我们来打架 要像个公鸡一样 你个胆小鬼
Come on! Fight me like a rooster, you weakling!
-拜托了 别这样  -快点
- Please, Tom! Stop! - Come on!
-停手 我不想打好吗  -你怎么那么没劲
- Stop. I don't want to, man! - Why are you such a cock?
我不想
I don't want to!
我不想这样
I don't wanna do it!
"我不想这样 我不想这样"
"I don't wanna do it! I don't wanna do it! I don't wanna do it!"
我也不想这样 格雷格
Neither do I, Greg!
我只是开个玩笑 笨蛋
It was a joke, you idiot.
你怎么这么不懂幽默
You're so hard to riff with.
这是你职业生涯中一个巨大的障碍
I mean that is a big career obstacle right there for you.
大得要命
Big!
别这样 朋友
Come on, man.
是啊 我猜...
Yeah, I guess the, uh...
对我来说 最实际最简单的办法可能是这样
the actual easiest thing for me would be, uh...
你懂的 肯德尔
you know, Kendall,
回头是岸 现在还来得及
probably isn't too late for you to backpedal on all your shit
你只要...
and just, you know...
认个错 或者混淆视听
say you were wrong or just fuzzle it up, you know.
退一步 让事态缓和下来
Just back off and cool it down.
这不可能
No, that's not possible.
我没做错 而且这样做会毁了我的声誉
I wasn't wrong and that destroys my reputation.
你应该听他的 儿子
You should listen to him, son.
这是怎么回事
Is this what this is?
-怎么回事  -什么
- What is this? - What?
你们俩把我骗到这来就是要搞定我这个刺头
I've been brought out here to be roughed up by the two of you?
-是这样吗  -不是
- Is that what this is? - No, no, no, no, no.
你就说"事情失去了控制 你搞错了
"Things just got out of hand. You were mistaken.
现在事态发展得过火了"
Things went too far".
不行 没门
No, no way.
那或许你稍微安分一点吗
Maybe just quiet down a little bit, all right?
你已经亮出了你的立场 不是吗 或许...
You've made your point, all right? Maybe just, you know...
我们应该不要再消费民众的愤怒
we could just close up the outrage shop.
让司法部去调查真相
Leave it for the DOJ to investigate.
你们俩是想在这里摆平我吗
Are you guys trying to fuck me here?
-肯...  -我看出来了
- Ken... - I see this!
别发火嘛 朋友
Easy. Easy, friend.
-好吧  -我们走吧
- All right. - Let's go.
你没事吧 儿子
You okay, son?
你嗑的那些药都把你搞成被害妄想症了
Some of those drugs you do can make you paranoid.
是不是
Is that right?
-好哇  -你好
- Hey! - Hi. Hi.
爸那边有什么进展吗
Any updates from Dad?
什么消息都没有
Radio silence, so...
要么一切顺利 要么...
either everything going to plan or...
他们刀剑相向同归于尽了
they've stabbed each other to death.
我们跟桑迪和斯图伊的谈判怎么样了
And where are we at with the Sandy and Stewy negotiation?
呃...
Oh, um...
不好意思
Pardon me.
暂时没谈成
Momentarily broken.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的 他们只是匆忙吃了点东西
Yeah, they're just grabbing a quick bite while they wait on
等着拿回文件
the turnaround of the document.
但整体氛围如何
But in terms of the temperature?
稍微有些不同意见 对吧
Uh, it's attritional, huh?
-没错  -很好
- Yeah. - Oh, great.
但我确认一下
But just so I'm clear,
我们究竟是卡在什么问题上呢
we're hung up on what exactly?
上次...
Well, the last, um...
分组会议是
break-out session was
停在有关非贬低条款的一些细节
some specifics about the non-disparagement clause.
[员工签署后即不能再发声反抗不当或非法行为]
我们还在谈这个吗
We're still on that?
我是说难道我们没有更重要的事情吗 比方说中止协议
I mean, don't we have bigger things like the stand-still?
[公司与潜在收购者之间的协议 包含管理如何购买 处置或投票公司股票等条款]
或许吧 但是...
Maybe, but...
我们真正想打探的是
what we're really trying to scope out here
是否真的存在议价空间
is if actually there is a deal space?
是啊 但我们时间够吗
Sure, but do we have time?
还是说我们就派你们两位大佬之一去那里...
Or do we just send one of you two big-hitters down there and...
然后逼他们就范 快刀斩乱麻
bang some heads together? Pull 'em out of the weeds, huh?
当然 这是种选择
It's an option. Sure.
很好
Great!
好吧 有重大新闻或变动...
Okay, well, I need big news or vibrations...
-告诉我  -一定的
- let me know. - We absolutely will.
谢谢 伙计们
Thanks, guys.
这里很不错吧
Ah, it's good, yeah?
是啊 很棒
Yeah. It's great.
你爸还好吗
Your dad's okay?
还好 他很好
Yeah, he's fine.
说吧 你有他的什么把柄
So, uh, come on. What do you have on him?
你知道的 我真的...
You know, I'd really...
不太想说 出于法律层面的考虑
rather not say. Legally.
我是说这应该挺难吧
I mean, I guess it's difficult, right?
你要是说你一无所知 就很假
I mean, if you have jack-shit you look like a fake.
你要是真有什么大招
If you have really damaging shit,
你或许会吓跑我 知道吗
you make me maybe want to run away, right?
他有所牵连
Well, he's implicated.
来了
Hey.
就随便聊两句
Just riffing.
在说我们的愿景
Pitching our vision.
我们走吧
Well, shall we?
喂
Yeah?
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hey!
雷文海德那边回绝了
Yeah, so, it's a no on Ravenhead.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh? - Yeah.
他认为自己不能胜任这个位置
He just doesn't see how he can accommodate the pivot.
-那太可惜了  -是啊
- Well, that's unfortunate. - Yeah.
他不是很乐意做这些
Yeah, he was fairly unpleasant about it all.
是吗 但我听说... 格雷格已经搞定了
Uh-huh? But I heard that... Greg's a lock.
对吗 他签了联合开发协议 所以...
Yeah? He signed the JDA, so...
[共同享受效益 共同承担风险的协议]
-你成功了  -是的
- You nailed that. - Yeah.
是我能应付的水准
That's about my level.
汤姆·威姆士丹 看管下属的受气包
Tom Wambsgans, minion wrangler and shit-eater.
好吧
Okay.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
是因为在上级那儿吃瘪吗
Is it the seniority thing?
-不是  -还是因为...
- No. - Or the...
你知道的 可能去坐牢
you know, the... prison possibility?
我只是...
I just...
我只是一直在想
I just keep thinking about, you know,
我们回家的时候
you know, when we get home,
在晚餐前我们喝了第一杯冷白葡萄酒
uh, before dinner we have that very first glass of cold white wine.
饿着肚子 你记得那杯非常冷的葡萄酒吗
On an empty stomach, you know that very cold glass of wine?
我太他妈爱了
I fucking love that!
我很爱喝 于是我...
I just love that and I...
我查了一下
And so I did a bit of research
然后我又再次耗在关于监狱的博文上了
and I got deep into the prison blogs again.
-亲爱的  -你知道吗 "监狱酒"
- Oh, honey! - You know, about "Toilet wine".
结果你用水果和蕃茄酱也可以制成
And turns out you can make it from fruit and ketchup
但你得在酒发酵的时候给它"排气"
but you have to "Burp" The wine back as it ferments.
我想"我要是忘记给监狱酒排气呢"
And I thought, "What if I forget to burp the toilet wine?"
但事实上 我在监狱里
But the truth is I'm not gonna get wine
不能喝到任何有温度的葡萄酒 小西
of any temperature in prison, Shiv.
监狱里没有好酒
There are no fine wines in prison.
你不能选择吃什么
You don't get to choose what you eat.
你不能决定做什么
You don't get to say what you do.
你知道吗 这就好像...
You know, like, like...
我能看书到多晚 什么时候"熄灯"
What... How late can I read? When is "Lights out"?
我... 我太害怕了 小西
I'm fucking... I'm fucking terrified, Shiv.
嘿 听我说 这...
Hey! Hey, it's...
我是说...
I mean, uh...
我不知道能和你说什么
I don't know what I can say to you.
我得...
Yeah, I gotta...
是爸打来的
It's Dad.
没关系 你接吧 你接吧
No. Sure, sure, sure, sure.
-抱歉 亲爱的 我...  -没事 没事
- Sorry, honey. I... - No. No, no.
-喂 爸  -我刚刚和卡尔谈过了
- Hey, Dad. - I've just spoken to Karl.
顺便告诉你 格雷格加入我们了 汤姆让他签了字
Uh, Greg's in by the way. Tom got him to sign.
卡尔不满意你的介入
Karl's not happy with your level of input.
是吗 好吧 去他的
Oh? Okay. Well, fuck him, right?
我不需要再生什么事端
I don't need another toothache.
是你同意我去那里教训他们的
Well, you okayed me to go in there and kick some ass.
而且我几乎没有...
And I barely...
我给了你一个目的地
I gave you a destination.
我不能陪你走到那 懂吗
I can't walk you there, okay?
当然 但是爸 如果你要向卡尔妥协
Okay, Dad, but if you give in to Karl,
那所有人都会开始排挤我
then everyone starts to carve me out.
有个限度
There's a line.
-还有...  -没什么是一成不变的
- And... - Nothing is a line.
万物皆在不断变化着
Everything everywhere is always moving forever.
趁早习惯吧
Get used to it.
好的
Okay.
乔希...
So, Josh...
我们谈到哪了
where are we on this?
你知道的 我妻子还在家里等着
You know, I have a wife at home.
谢谢
Uh, thank you.
那...
Well, uh...
请慢用吧
help yourself.
我基本上听明白了
Uh, I hear you on the fundamentals.
你知道的
You know.
去他的桑迪和斯图伊
I mean, fuck Sandy and Stewy.
那不过是金融资产重整
That's just financial engineering and...
我自己都能来 对吗
I can do that myself, right?
对 当然
Yeah, absolutely.
但是... 我还是不太能接受
But this... this still feels off.
肯 这好像...
I mean, Ken, it feels like...
你想让你爸蹲大牢吗
I mean, you want your dad to go to jail?
这不是我能说了算的
Well, uh, that's not for me to say.
但这差不多是你说了算
I mean, it kind of is, though.
如果你是法官 你希望他去坐牢吗
Like if you were a judge, you'd want him to go to prison?
我想传统的检举流程会被破坏
I believe the traditional whistleblowing process would be subverted.
-这就是为什么我...  -但是洛根
- So, that's why I... - Uh, but Logan,
要遭受名誉上的打击
the reputational hit?
我是说 世人看来或许你会成为...
I mean, optically, maybe you become...
一个笑话
a punchline.
那种无法东山再起的大人物
One of those big guys who aren't coming back.
冤冤相报何时了
When is this gonna end?
我听说你们是坐不同的飞机来的 我得说...
I'm hearing separate planes. I gotta say...
我不想把钱赌在家族夙仇上
I don't like betting on blood feuds.
最后会是我掌权...
It ends with me in control...
略施小惩
slapped wrists,
交罚金解决
and a payout.
这个问题
That stuff...
会像海雾一样
sea mist.
蒸发掉
Vapor.
这就是意见分歧的地方
Here's the disconnect.
听着 我认为...
See, I think that...
到头来...
end of the day...
你是为股东们效力
you work for the shareholders.
为我效力
For me.
但我发现你却认为
But I think that you think
我是在赌场上走了狗屎运的傻缺
that I'm some dipshit who had a lucky night at the casino,
还自命不凡
who acts all fancy,
让你们吃小老鼠来逗我开心 对吧
and then makes you eat fucking rodents for my pleasure. Right?
我的刀可就架在你们脖子上
But I have a gun at your head.
我只想知道这事到底能不能翻篇
And I need to know if this is gonna be a functional situation.
你们当然会说
And I'm sure you're gonna say,
"可以 这事可以翻篇"
"Yes, it is going to be a functional situation".
但我想看到你们真正把这事翻篇
But I'm gonna need to hear you say that it's a functional situation.
所以你们到底能不能并肩作战
So, can you work together?
-能  -当然 没问题
- Uh-huh. - Sure. Absolutely.
我去 够难搞的
Oh, fuck. This is tough.
不得不说 真他妈够难搞的 因为...
This is... It's fucking tough, I gotta say. 'Cause...
我信不过你们 真信不过
I don't really believe you. I mean, I kinda don't.
会好起来的
It'll be okay.
It'll be okay...
因为他是个好孩子
because he's a good kid.
-你说他是个好孩子  -对
- He's a good kid?  - Yeah.
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
-行  -他是的
- Okay. - Yeah.
他做了他觉得最正确的事情
He did what he thought was best.
虽然跑偏了 但是...
I think he went too far, but...
他是个好孩子
he's a good kid.
是吗
Yeah?
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid...
我很爱他
and I love him.
虽然...
I mean...
我们会付一大笔罚金
there'll be a big number.
他会抱头痛哭 但我呢... 会全盘接受
We'll pay, he'll mew and cry and... and I'll get it.
会好起来的
It'll all be okay.
然后
And...
也许...
maybe...
某天他会接班
it'll be him one day.
这是他的使命
It's in his blood.
都是我教给他的
He learned it all from me.
兴许...
And maybe...
兴许他就是几个孩子里最棒的那个
maybe he's the best one of all of them.
所以 没错
So, yeah...
会好起来的
it'll be okay.
行吧...
Well...
还挺暖心的
So, that's nice to hear?
是吧
Right?
所以 我想...
So, I guess...
要我加入你们的话 我有几个小心愿
for me to come your way, I have a little wish list.
我要一点股份 回购一些股票
A little EPS-juicing. Some stock buyback.
你知道的...
You know...
让我加入 好吗
let me in. Hmm?
听起来还不错
Sounds good.
我一定会考虑考虑
I'd consider that. Absolutely.
万分感激 洛根
I'd appreciate that, Logan.
这个电话我得接
Uh, I should take this.
咱们回程路上才能轻松一点
I want to make sure we get back a little easier.
都市佬
City boy, huh?
这附近可没什么咖啡厅和百吉饼店
Well, you're a bit far from your nearest coffee and bagel.
是啊
Yeah.
喂 是
Hello? Yes.
对
Uh, yes.
没错 没错
Sure, sure, yes.
怎么
What?
行 很好
Okay. Good.
行了
Okay?
那我们就回去吧 他们...
Look, shall we head back? They'll, uh...
他们会派代步车来接
They'll send some carts for us.
怎么样 你们想在这里等吗 我们也可以走到那边...
You good? You wanna wait here or we can walk up to the...
你... 要不要休息一下 老头
You wanna... You wanna rest up, old geezer?
我没事
I'm good.
行 那我们走过去吧
Good, let's do it.
说得真好啊刚才
Nice speeches.
确实
Yeah.
为了约会结束后能打一炮就是得不择手段 不是吗
Well, you'll say anything to get fucked on a date, won't you?
格雷格现在跟我了
You know, Greg's with me now.
他告诉你了吗
He tell you?
你现在孤苦伶仃了 孩子
You're on your own now, son.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
你现在立刻退休
Retire now, effective immediately,
或许我还会手下留情
maybe I go easy, row back.
你不出一个月就能拖垮公司
You'd scuttle the fleet in a month.
爸 我知道你是大哥大[银背金刚]
Dad, you're the silverback,
但我那天打倒了你 你没法东山再起了
but I put you in the ground that day. And you don't get to come back.
懂吗
Do you understand?
孩子 你知道吗
You know something, son?
我宁愿在淋浴室里让墨西哥佬干我
I'd sooner get fucked by a spic in a shower block
也不会把公司交你掌管
than see you have it.
老家伙任我使唤
And I got the Raisin under my thumb,
家人也都支持我 包括小格雷格
I've got the family, I've got little Greggy.
刺青男还在等我发号施令
I've got the fucking tattoo man in the tank.
你无依无靠
You're high and dry.
认命吧 孩子
Face it, son.
你输了
You lost.
你们能自己接着走吗
You guys good to keep going?
因为我有客人来了
'Cause, uh, I have visitors coming and, um...
你们能行吗 我得先走一步了
You sure you're okay? 'Cause I'm gonna run ahead.
-我可以派辆车来  -走吧 你走吧 我没事
- You go! You go! I'm great. - I could send a cart.
好
Okay.
乔希
Hey, Josh!
我感觉这条路是往海边的
Uh, I think this feels like it's going to the ocean.
不 这是条捷径
No, no, this is the short way.
放心吧 我认得路
Uh, anyway, I know where we are.
放心
Yeah.
别盯着我 我没事
Stop staring. I'm fine.
这条路很烂
Hey, it's pretty rough, though.
要不等车吧 这路上坑坑洼洼的
So, you wanna wait for the cart? I mean, there's a lot of bumps.
坑坑洼洼算什么
Oh, bumps! I've walked bumps!
你确定吗 我真的可以叫车
You sure? I don't mind calling.
我反正不需要
Oh, not for me. Not on my account.
是吧 肯
Right, Ken?
我们没事
We're good.
他状态很好 我们就用走的吧 爸爸
He's all good. Let's walk it out. Right, Dad?
他好着呢 他壮得像头熊
He's fine. He's a bear.
我先走一步
I'm gonna run up ahead.
你他妈连你需要喘口气都不愿意说吗
Can't you even fucking tell me you need a breather?
我没事
I'm fine.
可不是
Right.
你鬼话连篇 自己都不知道哪句真哪句假了
You've lied so much you don't even fucking know anymore.
脑子里都是浆糊 瞧你副这样子
Your brain's scrambled egg, look at you.
闭嘴吧 手下败将
I beat you. Pipe down!
什么 我听不见
What's that? I can't hear you.
你完蛋了
You're fucked.
是吗 你呢 都600岁了
Uh-huh, look at you. You're 600 years old
还能惹怒你的总统男友
and you've pissed off your fucking boyfriend,
他要派联邦调查局的人去抓你
the President, and he's sending the Feds on you
你想挣扎 无奈陷得太深
and you're wriggling, but you're in too deep.
大家都心知肚明
Everyone knows.
现在你想扭转局势
And now you're trying to counter
结果让小西掌权 可惜她鬼用没有
but you've put Shiv in there and she's a fucking dipshit.
听说没人把她当回事 大家都想赶她走
I hear no one respects her. Everyone's digging her out.
而你已经控制不了局面了 大家都恨你
And you're losing control, and everyone hates you.
先把和乔希的交易达成
Let's just close the deal with Josh.
他也恨你
He fucking hates you too.
就因为你那堆反犹太主义的百吉饼黄金屁话
Your anti-Semitic fucking bagel and gold bullshit!
滚蛋
Oh, fuck off!
你的话有一半都不过脑子
You don't even know what you're saying half the time.
感觉你真的就是不行了
It's like you're fucking losing it, man.
有没有水
You got water?
自己打电话要吧
Ask your fucking iPhone.
那啥 我得问问家里
Listen. I'm gonna call the house.
这条路确实是捷径 但有的时候会花费更长时间
'Cause, this is the quick way but sometimes it takes longer,
我打电话问问
so I'm checking.
-好  -行
- Okay. - All right.
喘口气 来吧 喘口气
Just catch your breath, okay? Catch your breath.
给我找个...
Get me something...
我要吐了
in case I puke.
我知道我在哪里 只是不知道你在哪里
Yeah, I know where I am. We don't know where you are.
所以迷路的是你 不是我们
Yeah, so, we're not lost. You're lost.
爸 别逞能了
Dad, come on.
还好吗
You okay?
没事的 跟他说
Yeah, yeah. Tell him. Yeah.
没事的
All good. All good.
你真的确定还好吗 老爸
Hey, listen to me. Are you okay?
你是不是心脏病发作了
Are you having a fucking heart attack here?
滚一边去
Fuck off!
我知道什么是心脏病发作 这次不是
I know what heart attacks are and this isn't one.
你...
You...
我觉得咱们需要台代步车 还有医生
I think we need a cart and a doctor.
别找医生 在他面前别找
No fucking doctor! Not in front of him!
我不想让你他妈的死在这儿
I don't want you fucking dying here.
你搞我是吧
You tried to fuck me!
我们得把你接回去 好吧 把你接回去
We need to get you back, okay? Let's just get you back.
爸
Dad!
乔希 我们得把我爸弄回去
Hey, Josh, uh, we need to get my dad back.
操了
Fuck! Fuck!
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
我去找个医生
I'm gonna get a doctor.
坚持住
Come on.
没事吧
Okay?
我没事
You know, I'm all right.
慢点吧 就在这坐下吧
Take it easy, right here. Take it easy. Sit down.
他娘的
Oh, fuck!
-好  -来
- Okay? - Yeah.
慢慢坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
你他妈到哪了
Where the fuck are you?
-我们需要医生  -好点了吗
- We need a doctor. - Okay?
好谢谢
Okay.
-对 对 谢了  -太晒了
- Yes, yes, thank you. - Too much sun.
他没事的 就是给晒着了
He'll be fine. Just a bit too much sun.
我们很好 对了 兄弟
We're good. Hey, listen, man.
-你知道...  -我觉得啊
- You know, I think, I think... - I think, maybe,
你现在想着照顾你爸就好了
why don't you just think about your dad right now, huh?
对吧 小肯
Right, Ken?
我可以谈一下玛格丽特校车事件
... but I could get talking about Margaret's school bus story.
你觉得呢 马克
What do you think, Mark?
我喜欢"恋童日托" 很有冲击力
I like "Pedo Daycare". It's strong.
别因为我打断了你们
Oh, no, don't let me interrupt.
你们继续 我在旁边等会就行
You carry on. I'll just wait in the corner.
我们就先结束吧 反正差不多了
Let's end there. I think we're pretty much done.
好极了
Great!
-你好  -我先给你打个预防针
- Hey. - Um, just so you know,
马克只跟希德或者洛根谈社论
Mark only discusses editorial with Cyd or Logan.
这是一直以来的惯例...
That's just been long-standing...
不 我不谈社论的事
Oh, no, that's fine. It's not editorial.
谢了 旺达
Thanks, Wanda.
-好啊  -好
- Hey! - Hi.
就是社论的事
It is editorial, so...
我有一行关于总统的台词
I have a line for you on the President
希望你能马上开始播报
that we'd like you to start rolling out immediately.
我们很乐意听听你的意见 但是
We're open to suggestions, but, uh,
我们就是觉得咱们在意识形态层面的支持
we just feel like our general ideological sympathy
也许让他们在太多细节上逃避了惩罚
has maybe let them off the hook on too many specifics.
对吧 比如科技巨头
Right? Like big tech.
中东问题
Middle East.
新能源补贴
Green subsidies.
我们需要夜间招牌档 比如...
We'd like a branded nightly segment, like...
"他是不是驾驭不住了"
"Is he losing his grip?"
你知道总统是我们这边的吧
You know he's a friend, right?
不是个问句吗 "是不是"
But with a question mark, like, "Is he?"
原来是个问句啊
Oh, with a question mark!
谢谢你允许我来自行决定句型
Well, thank you for giving me discretion on the punctuation.
小西 我是有个人观点的
Shiv, I have a perspective.
懂吗
Okay?
还有日积月累下来的名声
And a reputation that I've built up over a number of years.
可这是我父亲的要求
But this is something my dad wants.
第一 他的政治触觉十分敏锐
So, one, he has a great antenna
你应该相信他的直觉
and you should trust his hunches.
第二...
But two...
从某种意义上讲 这个对话已经结束了
in a sense, this conversation is already over.
接下来的问题只不过是
It's just a question of how many times
我们要和彼此对骂几个来回
we scream the word "Fuck" at each other
因为你一定会照办
before you do what we want.
如果我把你的威胁公开出去呢
What if I go public with this full-court press?
你会很难堪吧
Incredibly embarrassing for you.
是呀 不过...
Yeah, but...
其实你早该知道的 马克
the thing about us, Mark, and you should know this by now,
我们从来不会难堪
we don't get embarrassed.
我先进 谢了
After me. Thanks.
怎么样了
How're things looking?
会议在律师回去前通了电话
Conference call with lawyers before they head back in.
桑迪和斯图伊那边毫无进展 情况不容乐观
Sandy and Stewy. No progress. It's not good.
约会怎么样
And how was the date?
上床了还是上菜前给他打飞机了
Did you fuck him or tug him off between courses?
住嘴吧
Enough, okay?
-我认真的  -够了 住嘴
- Seriously, I mean it. - Enough. Stop it.
我认真的 别撩我了
Seriously, stop flirting with me.
你想干吗
What do you want?
你得高兴死
You're gonna fucking die.
-天啊  -我知道
- Oh, God! - I know.
别用这个
Don't use this.
不是吧... 这可是临门一脚
No! Come on... That is a magic bullet.
他会爱死 爸还会帮我洗澡澡
He's gonna love it. Dad's gonna give me my bedtime bath.
你当然可以把照片留下来 但是别散播
Bank the photos. By all means. But don't spread it around.
对洛根是好
Yeah, it's great for Logan.
但是对肯德尔不利 对你也不好
It's bad for Kendall. It's bad for you.
"纹身兄弟"
"The Tattoo Brothers"?
原来你这么在乎我吗
Oh, okay, so, what? You, uh... you care?
"这对我个人有何促进作用"
"How does this advance my personal position?"
你应该每时每刻都思考这个问题
You need to think about that 24/7.
没准应该把它纹在你额头上
You should get that tattooed on your head.
拿走
Here.
把照片放好 这是我们的小秘密
Keep the photos. Our little secret.
对了 你听说你爸的事了吗
Oh, did you hear about your dad?
没 怎么了
No, what?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是像那样控制他们的
I don't control them like that.
他有社论自由
He has editorial freedom.
得了吧 才没有 那只是谣言
Oh, come on, come on! That's just rumors.
看看节目
Watch the show!
我相信没那么严重
I'm sure it won't seem so bad.
你想听听
You want to hear what it sounds like
总统发飙的时候是什么样吗
when the President loses his temper?
听着 我来调查一下
Look, let me investigate. I...
你了解马克的 他既固执又独立
You know Mark. He's very tenacious, very independent.
要不是因为这破调查
I don't know, but if I wasn't so tied up
我已经分身乏术了
in this fucking investigation,
我肯定能专心让泛美网科输出官方观点
I could focus on keeping ATN on message. Hmm?
听说你又想杀了咱爸
Hey, I hear you tried to kill Dad again?
只是中暑
It was just heat exhaustion.
我们听说的可不是这样
Uh, that's not what we're hearing.
我们听说你差点把一个年迈的老人给晒死
We're hearing that you took an old man out to die in the sun.
我们和乔希走了一截
We went for a hike with Josh.
你想用太阳暗杀咱爸
You tried to assassinate our dad with the sun.
难道杀死爸爸能让你获得快感吗
Do you have a fetish for nearly killing Dad?
比如差一点点就能杀死爸的时候
Like, "Just the tip" But for like killing Dad?
听着 我搞定了
Well, look, it's in hand.
股东投票
The vote.
乔希稳了
Josh is a lock.
其实并没有 他退出了
Uh, well, no, actually. He's out.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
-他跟咱们一边的  -不 他退出了
- He's with us. - No! He's out.
弗兰克刚接到电话
Frank just got off the phone.
显然爸的小状况把他吓怕了
Apparently, Dad's little freak-out gave him the shits.
上层领导力差劲
Weak leadership, fractured at the top.
你任由咱爸蔫巴 还被乔希看见了
You let him fucking shrivel, he saw that.
现在他的原话是
And now he has, quote,
"对爸后期的领导力毫无信心"
"Zero faith in the post-Dad leadership".
这不是我的错 他已经老了爬不了坡
It's not my fault he's an old man who can't climb a fucking hill.
我们很快就会在股东大会上丢掉公司
We're about to lose the company at the shareholder meet,
全都是因为你没有及时给爸一瓶水
all because you wouldn't give our dad a timely fucking Evian.
妈的祝你好运吧
Good day!